Asuka

Nakajima



Contact

Address:

Tokyo-to Kita-ku Ukima 5-16-6 Sanshu Ukima

Phone:

+81 90 8177 7158

Email:

junizzanakajima@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

linkedin.com/in/nakajima-asuka

Languages

Japanese English Tagalog

Certifications

- HTML5 and CSS3
- Advance CSS3 and SASS
- JavaScript (ES5 and ES6+)
- JLPT N2
- TOEIC 955

Summary

As a self taught front-end web developer I have a huge thirst to learn new skills, and I strive to continue challenging myself. Experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, CSS3, SASS, OOP, JavaScript, Jquery, Bootstrap. Strong background in design, project management and customer relations.

Skill Highlights

- Responsive Web Design
- Website Speed and Performance
- BEM Methodology
- Good intuition on UX issues
- Service-focused

Experience

Project Manager - 09/2019 to 06/2020 **Wong Land Real Estate**, Philippines

- •Worked as a Project Manager and Interior Designer
- •Involved in concept designing and planning both interior and architectural projects
- •Provide oversight in the development of required project scopes and cost estimate for construction drawing and specification
- •Oversee various stages of the construction process
- Material control and payroll management

Interior Designer - 05/2018 to 08/2019 Studio Glitt, Tokyo, Japan

- •Worked as an Interior Design Assistant for International Projects
- •Involved in concept designing and planning awe-inspiring interiors
- •Proficient in 2D and 3D CAD programs in creating high-end compelling interiors
- •Japanese to English language interpretation for international clients on the design concept and intent
- •Official translator of the Japanese head designer and the internationally-based architect counterpart
- •Reviewed and adjusted detail shop drawing to align with international laws in America
- •Proofread of English to Japanese contracts and documents

Education

Online Course Certification: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript 9/2020 - 12 / 2020

Associate Degree: Interior Design 2016-2018

Space Design College, Tokyo, Japan

Language School: Japanese Language 2014-2015

Space Design College, Tokyo, Japan

Bachelors's Degree: Environmental Management 2009-2014

Miriam College, Manila, Philippines